François Beyers

St David's, Wales, United Kingdom



francois@beyers.tech



linkedin.com/in/francois-beyers

Summary

I am a freelancer and developer with a passion for creating digital products that leave the world in a better place. With 7 years of total experience, I have been a co-founder of Câr-y-Môr, a seaweed and shellfish farm, and a volunteer web designer for Catchafire. I have also served as a brand ambassador for TRIBE and worked as a software developer for a number of digital agencies. My skills include JavaScript, SEO, and WordPress development. I believe that software should improve someone's life and I am constantly striving to bring the world closer through technology.

Experience



Co-Founder

Câr-Y-Môr

Nov 2018 - Present (4 years 4 months)

Câr-y-Môr is committed to starting the first commercial seaweed and shellfish farm in Wales to motivate and inspire others to duplicate. This ZERO input farming uses no fertiliser, pesticides or fresh water. Our goal is to improve the coastal environment and well-being of the local community.

Volunteer, Web Designer

Catchafire

Aug 2020 - Present (2 years 7 months)

- Assist nonprofits with mission critical projects to advance their mission and goals
- Contributed approximately \$4,586 through 1 engagement with nonprofit organisations
- Learn more about my impact: https://www.catchafire.org/profiles/804323/impact/

TRIBE Brand Ambassador

TRIBE

Jan 2019 - Present (4 years 2 months)

Developer

Big Lemon

Apr 2022 - Jan 2023 (10 months)

As the headline says...

Building digital products that leave the world in a better place.

Working alongside an awesome team

Developer

Yellow Sub Hydro

May 2021 - Mar 2022 (11 months)

Radical Climate Change Adaptation and Resilience. Rising to meet the challenge of our time for the benefit of all stakeholders. #livelifeyellow #watersecurity #watercrisis #waterresources



Software Developer

Yellow Sub Creative Ltd

Jan 2021 - Mar 2022 (1 year 3 months)

I am a developer creating software that makes a difference. I believe that any software should be created to improve someone's life in some manner. Whether it's a tool for increasing productivity or giving people more entertainment options, there is always room for improvement. I am constantly trying to find new ways to bring the world closer together through technology and look forward to creating valuable products that will touch the lives of as many individuals as possible.



Full Stack Developer

21:32

Feb 2020 - Oct 2020 (9 months)

Yard Web Developer

Yard Digital

Apr 2019 - Feb 2020 (11 months)

JavaScript, jQuery, WordPress, Adobe Analytics, Google Analytics

Yard Junior Web Developer

Yard Digital

Jan 2018 - Apr 2019 (1 year 4 months)

As a developer at Yard, I am responsible for writing bespoke, custom code to capture data or fire tags, using Javascript, jQuery, and other web programming languages, to meet the specific requirements of the client. On occasions I could be required to develop technical tools or add-ons which are of relevance to the company's needs and ambitions in order to assist colleagues with their work.

Genius

Apple

Jul 2015 - Dec 2017 (2 years 6 months)

Using my problem-solving and people skills to ensure swift resolutions to technical problems of every kind. As a Genius, you provide insightful advice and friendly, hands-on technical support to Apple customers in need. I also educate my team members about products, while independently keeping my own technical know-how up to date.

Store Trainer

Apple

Jan 2017 - Mar 2017 (3 months)

- Responsible for training of all Apple employees in store.
- Delivered product, technical, customer service, system and new initiative training.
- Responsible for the induction and training of new employees.
- Responsible for the presenting and group activities within recruitment seminars.

- This role was a secondment.

Web Developer

FRNKDesign

Jan 2015 - Mar 2017 (2 years 3 months)

Bespoke Web Design for your business or even personal use. I bring a range of art and design disciplines to every project I work on. From brand strategy and user interface design to creative writing and front-end development.

Apple

Apr 2013 - Jul 2015 (2 years 4 months)

Process data transfers for windows or mac customers buying new machines. Conduct introductory personal training sessions with apple customers daily. Troubleshoot, repair and replace iPods, iPads and iPhones daily at the in-store Genius Bar. Provide iTunes technical support at the Genius bar instore daily.

Creative Contributor

Drift Surfing

May 2014 - Feb 2015 (10 months)

Writing Freelance articles about all things Surfing. Working on some other creative contributions to the website as well.

Specialist

Apple

Oct 2011 - Apr 2013 (1 year 7 months)

essic EXSIC Marketing Intern / UK Division

EXSIC

Aug 2011 - May 2012 (10 months)

EXSIC connects action sports business Founders, Owners, CEO's, & Managers together in one place to excel their passion for their sports and their companies together.

EXSIC's networking platforms covers members throughout North and South America, Europe, Australia, Asia and Africa. Join our online community with our EXSIC Memberships, or attend an EXSIC Event and meet action sports members from across the globe.

Education



Licenses & Certifications



- jQuery Essential Training Lynda.com
- React Native Essential Training Lynda.com
- Learning Google Tag Manager Lynda.com
- React.js Essential Training Lynda.com

Skills

Front-end Development • React.js • JavaScript • Web Development • Social Media Marketing • Marketing • Sports • Retail • Motion Graphics • Digital Marketing